let questions = [
  {
    numb: 1,
    question: "Is this artical REAL or FAKE news?",
    answer: "FAKE",
    options: [
      "REAL",
      "FAKE",
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 2,
    question: "Is this artical REAL or FAKE news?",
    answer: "REAL",
    options: [
      "REAL",
      "FAKE",
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 3,
    question: "Is this artical REAL or FAKE news?",
    answer: "FAKE",
    options: [
      "REAL",
      "FAKE",
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 4,
    question: "Is this artical REAL or FAKE news?",
    answer: "FAKE",
    options: [
      "REAL",
      "FAKE",
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 5,
    question: "Is this artical REAL or FAKE news?",
    answer: "REAL",
    options: [
      "REAL",
      "FAKE",
    ]
  },
  /* this is yet to be filled out */
  /*
  {
    numb: 5,
    question: "Is this artical REAL or FAKE news?",
    answer: "REAL",
    options: [
      "REAL",
      "FAKE",
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 6,
    question: "Is this artical REAL or FAKE news?",
    answer: "FAKE",
    options: [
      "REAL",
      "FAKE",
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 7,
    question: "Is this artical REAL or FAKE news?",
    answer: "FAKE",
    options: [
      "REAL",
      "FAKE",
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 8,
    question: "Is this artical REAL or FAKE news?",
    answer: "REAL",
    options: [
      "REAL",
      "FAKE",
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 9,
    question: "Is this artical REAL or FAKE news?",
    answer: "FAKE",
    options: [
      "REAL",
      "FAKE",
    ]
  } */
];